So, let us this course is made from basics.
So, I have started my course with the networking concepts.
So, the basic of networking, even I have covered the ports and protocols.
So, this is the foundational level of ethical hacking.
Before jumping on to the routine operations or broadening operations, we need to understand
how the, how two machines going to communicate each other.
So, I decided to put a section networking ok and the next thing will be jumpy count
to the lab setup, will be installing multiple softwares like virtual box and installing
Kali Linux, installing the Windows machine and even matter pattern machine ok.
So, every machines I have provided a separate link.
So, if you click on the external resource link, so you can directly move on to my google drive
and you can download it available ok.
So, next we will be going on to network different system.
So, we will be discussing what are the network different system available in the organizations.
We are going to discuss about firewall, IPS ideas, honey parts and other network difference
tools and India network detection and response platforms ok.
So, next we will be moving on to network based attacks, we will be performing few network
based attacks that was commonly performed by the detectors to take down a server or take
down some kind of cloud services.
So, once we complete that, we will be moving on to the vulnerability assessment using
NSSS.
So, we will be using the NSSS platform and we will be performing some kind of vulnerability
assessment and we will be finding out the vulnerability and making a server making the
vulnerability report.
Then, so once we complete the networking part and the vulnerability assessment part, we will
be diving into cyber security frameworks, we will be checking cyber field chain and brief
explanation of mitre attacks and how to submit if you find any program, if you find
any kind of application that will be harmful if you feel that will be harmful.
So, I just needed how to submit that file to mitre ok.
Then, we will be moving on to the end point different mechanism such as EDRs and antivirus
platforms and DLPs.
So, in this section, we will learn how EDRs will work, how antivirus officers will work
and how DLP will work ok.
So, because in this course, we discussed about different surveys and tactics and we bypass
few EDRs to bypassing the EDRs and different mechanism platform.
We need to understand how the defense mechanism has been architecture and how the defense
mechanism is working and it was structured.
Then, we will be jumping on to basic malware development, we will be developing a reverse
shell program and we will be getting a command and control from this ok.
This is the basic.
So, once we learned the very, very basic concepts, then we moving on to learn about our
machine.
You are going to target a Windows machine, you need to learn how Windows machine is operating
and how Windows machine is working and one of the things will be present in Windows
machine ok.
For example, our APIs, DLLs, processors, threads etcetera.
Next once we learned about our machine, we will be moving to logins, we will be calling
it as a living of the land binaries ok, scripts and binaries.
So, we discussed plenty of logins that was commonly abused by threat actors in lot of
incidents, lot of our ransomware attacks, even multiple explanations.
So, once we learned what is a login and how once we have a capability to handle the login,
then we will be jumping on to the initial access tactics, we will be following mitrotatics
and we discussed one by one attacks ok, we will be moving on to initial access, we discussed
plenty of initial access that was commonly followed by the threat actors to perform
my initial access or entering into the organization.
So, most of the videos we discussed practically even exploiting a Jenkins compromising the
credentials through RDPs exploiting the VPNs exploiting the SQLRC and multiple attacks
we have discussed in practical, even FTP exploitation.
So, once we complete that, we will be jumping on to the malware development intermediate
section.
So, we have developed huge malware like false injections, DLL injections and false
following attacks and even DLR hijacking.
So, once we jump, once we familiar in this section, we will be moving on to delivering additional
payroll inside the target machine.
So, in this section, we discussed about the Qbal Strike tool and encoding decoding, delivering
the payrolls, Qbal Strike payroll using login into the target machine.
So, once we complete that, we will be moving on to the privilege escalation section.
So, we will be jumping from user privilege to admin privilege and admin privilege to the
system privilege.
So, each and every attacks what we discussed, then we I have provided all the program
in Megitapropo.
You can you can use that and you can use in your test environment or if you need to practice
attack session.
So, once we complete the privilege escalation, we will be moving on to the current shell
axis.
We will be dumping else as and we will be watching what information will be stored in the
else as, we will be stealing the browser information, we will be using a lot of registry
types to perform to dump the database from the target.
So, next, we will be discussing about the persistence mechanism in the target machine,
we will be discussing like registry, startup items, WMI, services and scheduled tasks.
Once we complete that, we will be moving on to the different evasion tactics.
So, this is an also very important thing, we have bypassed EDRs and antivirus platforms.
We discussed lot of techniques in practically unhooking the EDRs, unhooking the DLLs, loading
new antivirus into the process and killing the different registries, adding exclusion,
killing the even logs and side loading, we discussed lot of things like patching a MSI.
Once we completed the different evasion tactics, we will be moving on to the discovery section
and we will be performing the internal scanning inside the organization.
Then we will discover what are the other hosts that was actively, that was active inside
the organization and we will be monitoring and we will be getting a record everything.
Once we get every record about the internal machines, so we will be performing a lateral
movement, we will be ready to jump from one machine to another machine.
So, a lateral movement, we discussed all, most of the impact library that was commonly
abused with the detectors to perform various attacks.
So, once we did that, we will be moving on to the collection section, we have used plenty
of applications like wind rare, some insect to collect the files on the target machine.
Once we done that, we will be moving on to the command and control section and we discussed
lot of applications that was commonly abused with the detectors to perform to initiate
the command and control tactics, even the any desk, team viewer and other armaboos.
So, once we complete that, we will be going to data exfiltration, we will be using some
kind of applications or some kind of softwares to perform a data exfiltration from the
machine, probably we will be uploading the files from the target machines to our problem.
So, once a data exfiltration has been completed, we will be moving on to the impact section
and we will be deleting some kind of recovery phases and we will be dropping a ransomware
and we will be installing the ransomware inside the environment.
So, this is the overall brief explanation of the course.
So, let me make sure you will be watching each and every fictions and each and every video.
Thank you for watching this video and see you guys.